<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>emoji on AiMinds</title>
    <link>https://aimindstech.github.io/tags/emoji/</link>
    <description>Recent content in emoji on AiMinds</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 AiMinds Inc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aimindstech.github.io/tags/emoji/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating Aha Products</title>
      <link>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Suppose you have been entrusted with the responsibility of seeking Innovation in your team/company to find the next big growth opportunity. Or you yourself have decided to take the plunge as an entrepreneur and be a disruptive innovator.
Where do you start? The theory of disruptive innovation itself does not tell you where to look for new opportunities. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t predict or explain specifically how a new company should innovate to undermine an established incumbent or where to create new markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disruptive Innovation</title>
      <link>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>Over the past few centuries we have seen lots of companies rise and doom. Usually when a company rises to a larger scale and commands a huge percentage of the market share - sustaining the same percentage of share over a long run is a challenging task.
For any company to retain the customer base over a long time usually requires a brilliant management team. Because Innovation transforms an existing market or sector by introducing simplicity, convenience, accessibility and affordability where complication and high cost have become the status quo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
