<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on AiMinds</title>
    <link>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on AiMinds</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 AiMinds Inc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aimindstech.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Inherent Randomness</title>
      <link>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>When was the last time you got into your car and worried about whether your car would start today? Those car owners from the 1980&amp;rsquo;s and 1990&amp;rsquo;s could vouch for this nightmare thought. So is this by accident that the cars manufactured today are not having this problem?
A typical car contains nearly 30000 individual parts in it. The complexity of taking so many things from so many different sources (suppliers) and turning them into a working car by itself is a miracle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Aha Products</title>
      <link>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Suppose you have been entrusted with the responsibility of seeking Innovation in your team/company to find the next big growth opportunity. Or you yourself have decided to take the plunge as an entrepreneur and be a disruptive innovator.
Where do you start? The theory of disruptive innovation itself does not tell you where to look for new opportunities. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t predict or explain specifically how a new company should innovate to undermine an established incumbent or where to create new markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disruptive Innovation</title>
      <link>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>Over the past few centuries we have seen lots of companies rise and doom. Usually when a company rises to a larger scale and commands a huge percentage of the market share - sustaining the same percentage of share over a long run is a challenging task.
For any company to retain the customer base over a long time usually requires a brilliant management team. Because Innovation transforms an existing market or sector by introducing simplicity, convenience, accessibility and affordability where complication and high cost have become the status quo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennial Business</title>
      <link>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>With abundance of choice and ease of accessibility of information, on anything and everything in this day and age, any purchase decision has indeed become a lengthy, tiresome process. In the pursuit of looking for the best deal all by ourselves, we spent countless hours of our time without even realizing it.
Say if we are looking to buy a property, most people do all the work of narrowing down the list of properties, visiting the open house all by themselves without involving any agents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wikipedia &amp; GDP</title>
      <link>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aimindstech.github.io/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Latest GDP statistics from the US and Canada shows almost a V shaped recovery could be still in the cards. With the second wave threatening to spoil the momentum, the course of the economic recovery will depend on our success in containing it.
But let&amp;rsquo;s take a step back and understand what GDP is. Wikipedia quotes &amp;ldquo;Gross domestic product (GDP) as a monetary measure of the market value of all the final goods and services produced in a specific time period&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
